/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data14_1', {
    title: '14.1 Multiply Decimal Numbers',
    path: '14.1-multiply-decimal-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{8.4}{6.7}}}',
                answer: '\\input{56.28}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{8.4}{6.7}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{0.4}{8.7}}}',
                answer: '\\input{3.48}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{0.4}{8.7}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{english}{partial}{8.7}{2.3}}}',
                answer: '\\input{20.01}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{8.7}{2.3}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{2.6}{2.3}}}',
                answer: '\\input{5.98}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{2.6}{2.3}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{english}{partial}{6.6}{4.4}}}',
                answer: '\\input{29.04}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{6.6}{4.4}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{3.4}{3.6}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12.24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{3.4}{3.6}}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{5.27}{1.3}}}',
                answer: '\\input{6.851}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{5.27}{1.3}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{english}{partial}{8.68}{39.8}}}',
                answer: '\\input{345.464}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{8.68}{39.8}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{english}{partial}{5.4}{3.18}}}',
                answer: '\\input{17.172}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{5.4}{3.18}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Multiply Decimal Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the product of the decimal numbers:}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\multiplydecimals{math}{partial}{1.39}{3.82}}}',
                answer: '\\input{5.3098}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\multiplydecimals{math}{complete}{1.39}{3.82}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
